[{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980269628,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":31388,"timeElapsed":68174},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980283313,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":13679,"timeElapsed":81859},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980297214,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":13895,"timeElapsed":95760},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980305883,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":8664,"timeElapsed":104429},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980323747,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":17860,"timeElapsed":122294},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980327065,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3314,"timeElapsed":125612},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980343765,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":16695,"timeElapsed":142312},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980347595,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":3825,"timeElapsed":146142},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980353481,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":5881,"timeElapsed":152027},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980758970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":404403,"timeElapsed":557516},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980765618,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6645,"timeElapsed":564165},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980772965,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":7343,"timeElapsed":571512},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980778768,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":5799,"timeElapsed":577315},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980781340,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":2568,"timeElapsed":579887},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980794136,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":12792,"timeElapsed":592683},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980796331,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":2191,"timeElapsed":594878},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980799548,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3214,"timeElapsed":598095},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980804050,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":4497,"timeElapsed":602597},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980808831,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":4777,"timeElapsed":607378},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980837747,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":27573,"timeElapsed":636293},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980846054,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":8304,"timeElapsed":644601},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980853114,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":7055,"timeElapsed":651660},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980857199,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4082,"timeElapsed":655746},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980879007,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":21804,"timeElapsed":677554},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980882073,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":3061,"timeElapsed":680620},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980886807,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4730,"timeElapsed":685353},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980889923,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":3113,"timeElapsed":688470},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980896091,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":6164,"timeElapsed":694638},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980906467,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":9350,"timeElapsed":705014},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980910532,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":4061,"timeElapsed":709079},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980918296,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":7760,"timeElapsed":716843},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980921138,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":2838,"timeElapsed":719685},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980929256,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":8114,"timeElapsed":727803},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980934654,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":5395,"timeElapsed":733201},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980944336,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":9670,"timeElapsed":742883},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980947768,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":3429,"timeElapsed":746315},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980951078,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":3305,"timeElapsed":749625},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980962714,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":10379,"timeElapsed":761261},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980965927,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3210,"timeElapsed":764474},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980970605,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":4674,"timeElapsed":769152},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980974586,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":3977,"timeElapsed":773133},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980978586,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3996,"timeElapsed":777133},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980982598,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":4008,"timeElapsed":781145},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980985178,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2576,"timeElapsed":783724},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980988445,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3263,"timeElapsed":786991},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980991172,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2724,"timeElapsed":789719},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981011277,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":17469,"timeElapsed":809824},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981013785,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":2504,"timeElapsed":812332},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981017769,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3980,"timeElapsed":816316},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981020194,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2420,"timeElapsed":818740},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981024083,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3885,"timeElapsed":822630},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981027185,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3098,"timeElapsed":825731},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981030681,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3493,"timeElapsed":829228},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981034080,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3395,"timeElapsed":832627},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981038058,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3974,"timeElapsed":836604},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981057442,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":18085,"timeElapsed":855989},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981060948,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":3502,"timeElapsed":859495},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981066627,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":5675,"timeElapsed":865174},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981068536,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1905,"timeElapsed":867083},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981072098,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":3558,"timeElapsed":870645},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981076685,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":4584,"timeElapsed":875232},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981082670,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":5982,"timeElapsed":881217},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981085892,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3218,"timeElapsed":884439},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981088533,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2637,"timeElapsed":887080},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981099715,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":9926,"timeElapsed":898262},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981102353,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2635,"timeElapsed":900900},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981106224,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3868,"timeElapsed":904771},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981173261,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":67033,"timeElapsed":971808},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981177596,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":4331,"timeElapsed":976143},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981181374,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":3775,"timeElapsed":979921},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981185426,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":4048,"timeElapsed":983973},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981189012,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3583,"timeElapsed":987559},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981192660,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":3645,"timeElapsed":991207},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981196536,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":3872,"timeElapsed":995083},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981410692,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":212968,"timeElapsed":1209239},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981413155,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2459,"timeElapsed":1211701},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981428692,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":15534,"timeElapsed":1227239},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981431861,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":3160,"timeElapsed":1230408},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981451321,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":19455,"timeElapsed":1249868},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981457326,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":6001,"timeElapsed":1255873},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981460635,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3305,"timeElapsed":1259182},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981464852,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":4213,"timeElapsed":1263399},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981468225,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3370,"timeElapsed":1266772},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981479935,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":10558,"timeElapsed":1278482},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981482769,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":2827,"timeElapsed":1281316},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981486296,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":3524,"timeElapsed":1284843},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981498000,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":11700,"timeElapsed":1296547},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981505412,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":7409,"timeElapsed":1303959},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981507984,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":2567,"timeElapsed":1306530},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981512478,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":4489,"timeElapsed":1311025},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981516897,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":4415,"timeElapsed":1315444},{"subjectID":"j6ucyooqbt","prolificID":"5c1ebf5f658e9200017ae7e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a8df7793f6e7def87","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981520304,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":3403,"timeElapsed":1318851}]